okay hello vertebrate hello everybody
好的，你好，脊椎动物，大家好
welcome to the session Java code
欢迎参加会议Java代码
coverage mechanics my name is Evgeniy
我是Evgeniy
man rakov and together with Mark Hofman
曼·拉科夫（Man Rakov）和马克·霍夫曼（Mark Hofman）
I'm one of the project leads of jacoco
我是jacoco的项目负责人之一
and
和
Eclipse echo I'm a project that you
Eclipse echo我是你的一个项目
might already know before we start the
在我们开始之前可能已经知道
usual disclaimer whatever I'm going to
通常的免责声明，无论我打算做什么
say has no connection with the company
说与公司无关
where I works on our source you might
我在我们的资料来源上工作的地方
know this one as well as it does such a
知道这一点，以及做到这一点
product as sonarqube static source code
产品作为声纳静态源代码
analyzer if you want to chat about this
分析器，如果你想聊天
you can catch me afterwards this
你以后可以抓到我
presentation is not going to be about
演讲将不会
that also before the starts for once
也是在一次开始之前
let's try to avoid cliche let's start
让我们尝试避免陈词滥调，让我们开始
from a questions more precisely
从更精确的问题
questions from me I'd like to know who
来自我的问题我想知道谁
came there to learn about code coverage
到那里来了解代码覆盖率
in general how to use it
一般如何使用
etc etc okay there are some sorry but
等等等等，好吧，但是有些遗憾
for you you still have a chance to leave
因为你仍然有机会离开
this room it's not going to be about
这个房间不会是关于
code coverage in general who is there
代码覆盖范围一般谁在那里
who already knows how to use code
谁已经知道如何使用代码
coverage and actually uses jacoco
覆盖范围并实际使用jacoco
library okay thank you
图书馆好了谢谢
who is there to learn something about
谁在那里学习有关
something new about Java okay good for
关于Java的一些新知识可以帮助
you also to say that we're going to talk
你也说我们要谈
about internal mechanics of Java and
关于Java的内部机制和
internals mechanics of code coverage not
代码覆盖范围的内部机制不是
about the actual results but about how
关于实际结果，但关于如何
we do obtain this result and sorry here
我们确实获得了这个结果，在这里对不起
is another disclaimer the real one we
是另一个免责声明，我们是真正的免责声明
are going to look into some internals of
将研究一些内部
G I am sorry facets we're going to talk
GI很抱歉，我们要谈谈
a strong language byte code again sorry
强大的语言字节码再次对不起
for that I will try this in half an hour
为此，我将在半小时内尝试
intense violence of your brain against
您的大脑遭受强烈的暴力侵害
surface that used to have a chance to
曾经有机会去的表面
live the room and be worn out there will
住房间，在那里穿会
be some implementation details please do
请提供一些实施细节
not rely on this dragon Zahir etc etc so
不依靠这条龙扎希尔等等等
let's start a bit of history of Java
让我们开始一些Java的历史
code coverage and jacoco and economic
代码覆盖率以及jacoco和经济
projects in particular all that started
项目特别是所有开始的项目
more than 10 years ago from such a nice
十多年前
library Emma which had if I'm not
艾玛图书馆如果没有的话
mistaken one and only one release this
误解了一个，只有一个发布了
was a library to gather code coverage
是一个收集代码覆盖率的图书馆
for Java
对于Java
it was develop it at a time of Java 5 as
它是在Java 5时代开发的
time yeah
是的
base it on this plugin sometime later
稍后再基于此插件
mark Othman started the project echo
马克·奥斯曼（Mark Othman）启动了该项目
Emma to bring code coverage into Eclipse
Emma将代码覆盖率引入Eclipse
ID some houses got quite popular it even
ID一些房子甚至很受欢迎
got some Eclipse community alerts but as
得到了一些Eclipse社区警报，但是
time was going on it became obvious that
时间流逝，很明显，
Emma doesn't evolve whereas there is a
艾玛（Emma）不会进化，而有一个
need to support a new Java versions new
需要支持新的Java版本
GT case new juries etc so sometime later
GT案新陪审团等
mark also started another project a new
马克还开始了另一个新项目
library for for Java code coverage a
Java代码覆盖库
little bit later I joined his efforts
后来我加入了他的努力
echo Emma its second version was fully
呼应艾玛的第二版
based it on a new library and let's say
基于一个新的图书馆，我们说
a year ago we decided to move echo Emma
一年前，我们决定移动echo Emma
into Eclipse Foundation it's now
现在进入Eclipse Foundation
official Eclipse project but it's not
官方的Eclipse项目，但不是
that important for this talk um one
这对这次谈话很重要
interesting funny fact even those emma
有趣的有趣事实，甚至那些艾玛
plugin sorry Emma library is a library
插件对不起Emma库是一个库
for code coverage for code coverage by
代码覆盖率
tests
测试
actually there were no single unit tests
实际上没有单个单元测试
in this library let's move on as we are
在这个库中，让我们继续前进
talking about some measurement which is
谈论一些测量
code coverage it's important to remind
代码覆盖率，重要的是要提醒
you an observer effect so here is a big
你是一个观察者，所以这是一个很大的
quote from Wikipedia simplifying call
Wikipedia简化通话的报价
this observer effect is that any kind of
这种观察者效应是
measurement any kind of instrumentation
测量任何一种仪器
any way is going to alter the state of
任何方式都会改变状态
what is measured so anyways there is
被测量的东西无论如何都存在
some side effect of measure and cut
削减的一些副作用
coverage and this is important for us a
覆盖范围，这对我们很重要
users it's important to know about this
用户，了解这一点很重要
for us as a developers it's also
对于我们作为开发人员来说
important to know about this in order to
了解这一点很重要，以便
try to minimize this effect in order to
尽量减少这种影响，以便
try to minimize performance impact in
尽量减少对性能的影响
order to not change the behavior of the
为了不改变行为
application otherwise we're measuring
应用程序，否则我们正在衡量
something strange we are not measuring
我们没有测量的奇怪东西
actually your application but something
实际上是您的应用程序但是
which changes the behavior etc etc so
这会改变行为等
let's have a look how we achieve all
让我们看看我们如何实现所有目标
these so how how can we record execution
这些如何记录执行情况
of some applications there is several
在某些应用程序中，有几个
approaches to this one of this approach
这种方法之一
is some runtime profile link you can use
是您可以使用的一些运行时配置文件链接
some interfaces gbmpid gmj etcetera
一些接口gbmpid gmj etcetera
etcetera
等等
another approach you can do
你可以做的另一种方法
instrumentation you can modify what is
仪器可以修改什么
executed in a way sets will allow you to
以一套方式执行将使您能够
record the execution process and that's
记录执行过程，那是
a that's usually the approach that is
通常是这样的方法
taken by code coverage tools and jacoco
被代码覆盖工具和jacoco所采用
is not exception one of such
也不例外
instrumentation approaches you can
您可以采用的检测方法
modify the source code
修改源代码
this approach is taken by Atlassian
这种方法是由Atlassian采用的
clover library another approach you can
三叶草库您可以使用的另一种方法
modify the bytecode as a result of
修改字节码的结果是
compilation of the source code
源码汇编
for the modification of bite cuts you
咬的修饰会削减你
also have two options you can do this
也有两个选择，你可以做到这一点
so-called in a flying mode before I know
所谓的飞行模式才知道
your application you prepare your
您的应用程序，您准备您的
classes you instrument them and another
您对它们进行测量的班级和另一个
approach is to do exactly the same
方法是做完全一样的
transformation but to do this at runtime
转换，但要在运行时执行
so transparently for your build process
对您的构建过程如此透明
without touching actual class files on a
无需触摸实际的班级文件
disk
磁碟
Juuko implements both approaches they
Juuko实施了两种方法
both has pros cons etc etc and as JUCO
都有利弊等，并作为JUCO
works on byte codes it's quite important
在字节码上工作非常重要
to put exclamation mark on ZZZ Jaco
在ZZZ Jaco上加上感叹号
works on class files only
仅适用于类文件
it doesn't need actually a source files
它实际上不需要源文件
so how it works we have a class file we
所以它是如何工作的，我们有一个类文件
do instrumentation we do modification of
做仪器，我们做的修改
this class file with a modification of
此类文件的修改
bytecode then we do execution of of what
字节码，然后我们执行什么
we just modified this process of
我们只是修改了
execution is going to record the
执行将记录
information about execution in some
有关执行的信息
binary format which we call exec and at
二进制格式，我们称为exec和at
the time of report analysis we again
我们再次进行报告分析的时间
take original class files and this is
拿原始的班级文件，这是
also important original Crossfire's not
同样重要的原始交火
some other class files but but really
其他一些类文件，但实际上
Zeus which we instrumented we combined
我们组合的宙斯
the original class files with with
原始类文件与
execution data then we do analyzes and
执行数据，然后我们进行分析，
we get a report and source code plays a
我们得到一个报告，源代码播放
role only in the UI so just to display
角色仅在用户界面中显示
you the nice highlight and copy a source
您不错的亮点并复制源
code this is the only moment when source
编写代码，这是获得源代码的唯一时刻
code plays the wrong if you don't have
如果没有，代码播放错误
source code we anyway can tell you this
我们无论如何都可以告诉您的源代码
amount of lines has been covered this
线的数量已被覆盖
amount of methods has been covered and
方法的数量已经涵盖，
etc etc and yeah speaking about how to
等等等，是的，关于如何
integrate all these into a build process
将所有这些集成到构建过程中
it's as easy as setting one argument for
这就像为一个参数设置一样简单
the JVM we need to attach so-called Java
我们需要附加所谓的Java的JVM
agent which will perform in
将执行的代理
mutation and transformation of the byte
字节的突变和转换
code this Java agent implemented
此Java代理实现的代码
something like this it starts after the
这样的事情会在
JVM startup but before the startup of
JVM启动但启动之前
your application this Java agent has a
您的应用程序此Java代理具有
capability to say okay any class that
可以说任何课程的能力
JVM is gonna load I'd like to have a
JVM将要加载，我想拥有一个
chance to transform its bytecode let's
有机会转换其字节码
have a look on what these byte codes
看看这些字节码是什么
transformation is on the slide you can
您可以在幻灯片上进行转换
see some control flow graph of some
看到一些控制流程图
application you have some sequences of
应用程序有一些顺序
instructions you have some conditional
说明你有条件
jumps you have entry point you have exit
跳，你有入口点，你有出口
point and in order to record the
点并为了记录
execution process just in certain places
只是在某些地方执行过程
of this control flow we need to insert
我们需要插入此控制流
so-called props so for example if prop
所谓的道具，例如，如果道具
at the bottom is rigid if we know that
如果我们知道，底部是刚性的
this piece of code was executed then we
这段代码已执行，然后我们
know that the exit of the method was
知道方法的退出是
Richard if the left prop was Richard
理查德（如果左支柱是理查德）
then we know okay one branch of
那我们知道一个分支
conditional jump was Richard if you know
如果你知道，有条件跳就是理查德
that the right prop was Richard we know
我们知道正确的道具是理查德
that another branch of conditional jump
有条件跳跃的另一个分支
was reached a little bit more precisely
更精确地到达了
on how do we insert those props if you
关于如何插入这些道具，如果您
have a sequence of some bad cut
有一些不好的结果
instructions it's it's incredibly easy
说明，这是非常容易的
you just can insert your prop in between
你可以在两者之间插入道具
two instructions and you will know that
两条指令，您将知道
if this prop is executed then all
如果执行了这个道具，那么所有
instructions before this probe has been
进行此探针之前的说明
executed if we have exit of a method
如果有方法退出则执行
it's a little bit more tricky you can't
这有点棘手，你不能
put your prop after the exit you need to
离开出口后放好道具
put it a little bit before so we place
先放一点，然后放置
it just before the return from the
它刚从返回
method if you have a jump it's pretty
方法，如果你有一个跳跃，这很漂亮
much similar to the exit of the method
与方法的退出非常相似
you you place the prop
你把道具
before the jump if prop is executed you
如果执行了道具，则在跳转之前
know that jump was executed in case of
知道在以下情况下执行了跳转
conditional branches conditional jumps
有条件的分支有条件的跳跃
it's a little bit more tricky but
有点棘手，但是
basically you just need to know the fact
基本上你只需要知道事实
which branches cover it so you insert
哪个分支覆盖它，所以您插入
drop on one of those branches and if it
放在那些分支之一上，如果它
is executed you know that this branch
被执行，你知道这个分支
was executed and you can imagine that
被执行了，你可以想象
all this was just the basic strategies
所有这些只是基本策略
and Java compiler actually generates far
Java编译器实际上产生了
more sophisticated combinations of Zeus
宙斯的更复杂的组合
and so all these needed to be tested and
所以所有这些都需要测试
to do such distinct we have so called
做如此独特的事情
Joko validation test suit we write
我们编写的Joko验证测试服
various different pieces of java code to
各种不同的Java代码片段
verify that and and purifies that record
验证并清除该记录
at code coverage and the reported result
代码覆盖率和报告结果
is an is the ones that we expect we do
是我们期望我们做的
this by annotating the source code with
通过注释源代码
special markers later on we can do
以后我们可以做特殊标记
assertions on Zeus markers same Koki
关于宙斯标记的断言相同
what happened it's at a line where we
发生什么事了
have a while loop etc etcetera and so we
有一个while循环等等等，所以我们
execute this test suit on five major GDK
在五个主要的GDK上执行此测试服
versions we support Java agents were
我们支持Java代理的版本是
introduced it in Java five so this is
在Java 5中介绍了它，所以这是
our minimal supported target maximal
我们的最小支持目标最大值
support at one as of today is Java nine
Java截至今天的支持数为9
we also do testing of early access
我们还进行了抢先测试
builds and thanks to all this testing we
建立，并感谢所有这些测试，我们
dint affine not only issues and in
仿射仿射不仅在问题上而且在
jacoco but also actually issues in open
雅各，但实际上也公开
JDK if I may say I would even say we
如果我可以说JDK，甚至可以说我们
mainly find issues in open to decane not
主要发现对癸烷不开放的问题
enjoy cocoa and apparently we are among
享受可可，显然我们在其中
top five external contributors of back
返回的前五名外部贡献者
reports to openjdk along such projects
向openjdk报告此类项目
as actually seen IntelliJ etcetera
正如实际看到的IntelliJ etcetera
etcetera and actually this is not that
etcetera，实际上这不是那个
hard as you might think during this
您在此期间可能会觉得困难
presentation let's we will see how easy
演示文稿，我们将看到多么容易
it is to find the back in open JDK and
它是在打开的JDK中找到背景并且
it's not that hard to come back and
回来并不难，
report it so to do so let's have a look
报告此操作，让我们看一下
more deeper on what prop is why it is
更深入地了解什么是道具
quite fast why it has no impact on why
非常快，为什么对为什么没有影响
it has a low impact on your application
它对您的应用程序影响很小
and some so what the prop is first
还有一些道具是什么
before before implements the prop we
在实施道具之前
should specify the requirements what
应该规定要求什么
it's supposed to do and prop as we
它应该像我们一样做和支撑
already said it should have minimal
已经说过了
runtime overhead it should be as fast as
运行时开销应该和
possible it should have no side effects
可能没有副作用
on application code in particular if
尤其是在应用程序代码上
you've got this thread safe it should
你有这个线程安全，应该
stay state right safe so we can't have
保持国家安全，所以我们不能
non threat safe code yeah so it should
非威胁安全代码是的，所以应该
be thread safe obviously it should
是线程安全的，显然应该
record the fact of execution so which it
记录下执行的事实
should say okay I've been executed and
应该说好，我已经被处决了，
if you just record fact of execution we
如果您只记录执行事实，我们
can't map it back to the what was
无法将其映射回原来的位置
executed so it should also be
被执行，所以也应该
identifiable so it should provide some
可识别的，因此应该提供一些
way of identifying what was actually
识别实际上是什么的方法
executed okay and here is another
执行好了，这是另一个
question for you
给你的问题
maybe you have some ideas how such prop
也许你有一些想法，这样的道具
could look like any ideas
看起来像任何想法
something like a bull honoring exactly
像公牛一样的东西
it perfectly meets all the requirements
完全满足所有要求
array index provides us identification
数组索引为我们提供了识别
what else it's quite fast writing of a
还有什么是相当快的写作
value into the boolean array so it will
值放入布尔数组，因此它将
record an execution if if we wrote a
如果我们写了一个
true value into this boolean array for
布尔数组中的真实值
some identifier we know that the code
一些标识符，我们知道代码
associated let's say this is identifier
关联，假设这是标识符
has been executed and here is another
已经执行了，这是另一个
question why this is thread safe what if
问题为什么这是线程安全的，如果
the same prop is executed multiple times
多次执行同一道具
sent from concurrent threads
从并发线程发送
okay arrays initialize it indeed it's
好的数组初始化它确实是
and solids defer yes it's it's just
和固体推迟是的，只是
right and there is no reads so there is
对，没有读，所以有
no chance for it to not be trade safe if
如果没有机会，它就没有交易安全的机会
two threads are going to write a true
两个线程将要写一个真实的
value it doesn't matter which one
重视哪一个都不重要
succeeded which one not there is any way
成功了，那是没有办法的
we'll get through Valley about runtime
我们将了解有关运行时的Valley
overhead and about impact on the size of
开销以及对文件大小的影响
your class files each such probe costs
您的课程会记录每个此类探查成本
from 4 to 7 bytes additional bytes so
从4到7个字节增加了字节
depending on how many probes we had we
取决于我们有多少探头
had a proportional amount of bytes into
有成比例的字节进入
your classes this is also an interesting
您的课程也很有趣
aspect some people wonder why after we
方面有些人想知道为什么我们之后
integrated code coverage into our
将代码覆盖范围整合到我们的
project we started to get exceptions
我们开始获得例外的项目
something like method is too big because
方法之类的东西太大，因为
there is no free lunch there is a
没有免费的午餐，有一个
restriction in Java Virtual Machine on a
Java虚拟机上的限制
maximum size of often added and as we
通常添加的最大大小
adding some additional instructions into
在其中添加一些其他说明
this method if you method was close to
如果您的方法接近
the border we can easily cross this
我们可以轻松跨越这个边界
border after addition of those
那些添加后的边界
instructions bomb next so ok this is the
指示炸弹接下来，好的，这是
process of recording execution of some
记录一些执行的过程
sequence of instructions and well we've
指令的顺序，我们已经
been discussing this we also mentioned
在讨论这个我们也提到
that this array should be naturalized so
该数组应归纳为
there is a jagged current time and then
现在有一个锯齿状的时间，然后
the ratio application and somehow your
比率应用程序以及您的某种方式
applications that contains access to
包含访问权限的应用程序
this array should should get this array
这个数组应该得到这个数组
from jaco current time and so how do we
从雅各当前时间开始，那么我们该如何
get this array from Joe Cocker on time
准时从Joe Cocker获得此阵列
in order to answer on this question
为了回答这个问题
let's have a look on bytecode of
让我们来看看
assertions let's say I have such a
断言，假设我有这样一个
simple class it has only one method in
简单的类，它只有一种方法
this method I do I search shown on the
我搜索的这种方法显示在
parameter
参数
there is a nice - in GDK called java p
有一个不错的-在GDK中叫做java p
java decompiler which can given a class
可以给一个类的java反编译器
file it can show you the bytecode
文件可以显示字节码
instructions within this class file so
该类文件中的说明，因此
here is a result of the compilation of
这是编译的结果
such a simple program and here we can
这样简单的程序，在这里我们可以
see something strange in this de
在这个地方看到一些奇怪的东西
compilation we actually see that there
编译我们实际上看到那里
is multiple conditions there is two
有多个条件有两个
comparisons if not equal if not equal
如果不相等则比较
there is also access to a static field
也可以访问静态字段
which called whose name is assertions
哪一个叫断言
disabled and somehow we didn't wrote
残疾人，但我们没有写
north two conditions in our source code
我们的源代码中的北两个条件
nor we have no such field what what is
我们也没有这样的领域
that and to simplify your life a little
这样可以简化您的生活
bit
一点
apparently in order to implement
显然是为了实施
assertions Java compiler while compiling
编译时声明Java编译器
your source code generates a quite
您的源代码生成了一个相当
interesting bytecode as we have seen it
我们看到的有趣的字节码
injects a special field into your class
为您的班级注入一个特殊的领域
with the name dollar assertions disabled
名称断言被禁用
then each assertion is transformed it
然后每个断言都被转换
into the indeed two conditions one of
进入以下两个条件之一
the conditions is to check the value of
条件是检查
this field and another condition is an
这个领域和另一个条件是
actual condition of assertion and why
断言的实际情况以及原因
compiler does this the answer is is
编译器这样做的答案是
pretty simple it's in order to reduce
很简单，是为了减少
overheads so for example you know that
间接费用，例如，您知道
you can disable assertions you can
你可以禁用断言
enable assertions and for the given
启用断言并针对给定
class in order to know whether
为了知道是否上课
assertions are enabled or disabled for
断言的启用或禁用
this class you need to ask the JVM could
此类，您需要询问JVM是否可以
you please tell me the current status of
您可以告诉我...的当前状态
assertions for this class this is quite
对于这个类的断言这是相当
expensive procedure you need to go to
您需要去的昂贵的程序
some runtime this runtime needs to check
一些运行时，此运行时需要检查
some property
一些财产
is etc etc so in order to reduce this
等等等，以减少这一点
overheads a trick is simple
开销很简单
let's ask once during initialization of
让我们在初始化期间询问一次
this static final field and then later
此静态最终字段，然后再进行
on let's reduce the results that we
让我们减少结果，
already know and the important thing to
已经知道，重要的是
notice here is that compiler generated
注意这里是编译器生成的
constructions a market as synthetic we
建立合成市场
will see later on why this is important
稍后会看到为什么这很重要
this is a nice idea which we can use and
这是一个好主意，我们可以使用
which we actually do use for jacoco in
我们实际上在
order to reduce the runtime overhead of
为了减少运行时的开销
getting the probes array we do the same
得到探针数组，我们做同样的事情
trick we ask for this probe array once
技巧，我们一次要求这个探针阵列
we store it into a synthetic field
我们将其存储到一个合成领域
pretty much like assertions enabled and
非常像启用断言和
then we simply access this field
然后我们只需访问该字段
similarly to the java compiler we mark
与我们标记的Java编译器类似
this field as synthetic and for the
该领域是合成的，对于
users of jocose this is also important
使用者的追逐这也很重要
to know some people after applying
申请后认识一些人
jacoco on their project start to wonder
jacoco在他们的项目上开始感到奇怪
why the codes that uses reflection
为什么使用反射的代码
apparently starts to see some some
显然开始看到一些
stretch fields that they never brought
伸展他们从未带来的田野
and the answer is that the code is not
答案是代码不是
ignoring synthetic constructions whereas
忽略合成构造，而
it should so please fix your refraction
应该这样，请修正您的屈光度
to ignore the synthetic constructions
忽略合成结构
you can get zeus even with plain simple
即使简单也可以得到宙斯
stupid java sources not only this joke
愚蠢的java来源不只是这个玩笑
oka let's move on a neck and next
好吧，让我们继续前进
question from me so you know already
向我提问，所以你已经知道了
that there is some synthetic
有一些合成的
constructions that Java compiler
Java编译器的构造
generates do you have any ideas of other
你对其他有什么想法吗
synthetic constructions exactly bridge
合成结构正好成为桥梁
method so one bridge methods so one of
方法如此之一桥梁方法之一
examples of bridge methods we have outer
我们有外部的桥梁方法的例子
class we have inner class inner class
上课我们有内在课
does an access of private fields of an
可以访问
outer class
外层阶级
according to the Java language
根据Java语言
specifications this is perfectly valid
规格，这是完全有效的
and this is permitted however according
而这是允许的，但是根据
to Java Virtual Machine specification
Java虚拟机规范
these two classes they are in the same
这两个类在同一个
package and in your class actually can't
包，在你的课上实际上不能
access private fields of an outer class
访问外部类的私有字段
so in order to avoid what says this a
所以为了避免这说什么
little misalignment between Java
Java之间的少许偏差
language specification and virtual
语言规范和虚拟
machine specification compiler generates
机器规格编译器生成
so-called bridge methods again if we do
所谓的桥梁方法
compile our classes we can see that
编译我们的课程，我们可以看到
outer class after compilation it has
外层类编译后具有
special methods with some generated name
具有一些生成名称的特殊方法
access something which is again market
访问又是市场的东西
as synthetic and if we compile inner
作为合成的，如果我们编译内部
class we will see that access of field
上课，我们将看到字段的访问
is actually performed through the
实际上是通过
through the generated synthetic method
通过生成的合成方法
what about methods in enums you know
你知道的枚举中的方法呢
that if we declare in ohm with some
如果我们在欧姆中声明一些
constants we will get two additional
常数，我们将获得两个附加值
methods generated by Java compiler
Java编译器生成的方法
values and value of as a synthetic then
值和合成的值
not this is a common misbelief that
这不是一个普遍的误解，
everything generated by Java compiler is
Java编译器生成的所有内容都是
synthetic no this method are not in
合成否此方法不在
synthetic and the reason for this is
合成的，原因是
Java compiler doesn't wouldn't allow you
Java编译器不允许您
to explicitly refer to some synthetic so
明确地提到一些合成的
you can't write a code that will compile
你不能写一个可以编译的代码
and it that will that will use synthetic
它会使用合成的
methods synthetic fields and as those
方法合成领域和那些
two methods in enums values and value of
枚举值和值的两种方法
they are intended to be accessible by
它们旨在被
developers they are not synthetic
开发商他们不是合成的
this is important for code coverage
这对于代码覆盖率很重要
tools because you don't need to test the
工具，因为您不需要测试
code that is generated by compiler
编译器生成的代码
you're gonna trust the compiler so this
您将信任编译器，所以这
method should be actually excluded from
方法实际上应该从
the coverage analyzers let's move
覆盖率分析仪让我们开始前进
forward another interesting example of
转发另一个有趣的例子
synthetic constructions generated by
由...生成的合成结构
Java compiler is implementation of
Java编译器的实现
lambdas so if you have a lambda like
lambda，所以如果您有lambda
implementation of functional interface
功能接口的实现
runnable like this again if you D
如果您D再一次像这样运行
compile it and here you might learn some
编译它，在这里您可能会学到一些
new option for java decompiler - L which
Java反编译器的新选项-L其中
will display you align numbers in the de
将在de中显示您的对齐数字
compiled at code you will see that
在代码中编译，您将看到
within this class you will have one more
在这堂课中，您将再有一个
synthetic methods whose name starts with
名称以开头的合成方法
lambdas and something generated and
lambda和产生的某些东西
actually the content of this method
实际上这个方法的内容
lines lines within this methods a map
在此方法中的线
one two one two the lines of your lambda
一二一二你的lambda
this is this is again before nuts
这又是坚果之前
dragons here this is implementation
龙在这里这是实现
details of lambdas there is no guarantee
Lambda的详细信息无法保证
that tomorrow this wouldn't change why
那明天不会改变为什么
this is important for code coverage as
这对于代码覆盖率很重要，因为
we said before some methods and
我们说过一些方法之前，
specifically the ones generated by
特别是那些由
compilers synthetic and not synthetic we
编译器合成而不是合成我们
should ignore for code coverage
应该忽略代码覆盖率
whereas for lambdas even zoos its market
而对于lambdas甚至动物园来说，其市场
a synthetic we shouldn't ignore it
合成的，我们不应该忽略它
because you want a coverage of your
因为你想要覆盖你的
numbers
数字
how we do all these manipulations with
我们如何进行所有这些操作
with bytecodes
带字节码
we rely on on a such a great library as
我们依靠如此强大的图书馆
Isum
五十胜
which allows us readings a bytecode
这使我们可以读取字节码
writing the byte codes etc etc and here
写字节码等等等在这里
is an interesting funny fact which is
这是一个有趣的有趣事实
connected with how to support how how we
连接如何支持我们如何
did brought a support of Java 9 so if we
确实带来了对Java 9的支持，所以如果我们
will take Java compiler from early
从早期开始将采用Java编译器
access build of gdk9 if we will compile
如果我们要编译，请访问gdk9的构建
some class into the bytecode of Java 9
一些类到Java 9的字节码中
and if we will try to use by some
如果我们尝试使用某些
library at that time on this class file
当时在该类文件上的库
we will actually get illegal argument
我们实际上会得到非法论点
exception and the reason for this I same
例外和我相同的原因
library hasn't yet been updated for Java
Java的库尚未更新
so how we can support the Java 9 before
那么我们之前如何支持Java 9
an actual release of SM which probably
SM的实际发行版
will happen after the release of Java 9
将在Java 9发布后发生
which is a little bit late for us and
对我们来说有点晚了
yeah interesting fact fact if on the
是的，如果在
same class file we will use the standard
同一类文件，我们将使用标准
java decompiler even its old version
java decompiler甚至旧版本
like version 1.7 then actually it will
像1.7版一样，实际上
have no problem to decompile this class
没有问题可以反编译此类
it will show ok this this class file has
该类文件将显示确定
a major version number ZZZ which I
我的主要版本号ZZZ
probably do not very well support but
可能不是很好的支持，但
there won't be any illegal argument
不会有任何非法论点
exception what this the compiler can do
例外，编译器可以做什么
compile it to the compiled and what it
将其编译为已编译的内容
can't it can't it's a pretty much the
不能，不能，几乎是
same story oh sorry
同样的故事，对不起
another hidden gem of this the compiler
编译器的另一个隐藏的宝石
is that you can actually use some hidden
是你实际上可以使用一些隐藏的
flags like - - - cigs details and you
像---的标志会标记详细信息，而您
can actually
可以实际
see not only the white coats you can
不仅可以看到白大褂
also see the bytecode alongside with the
也可以看到字节码和
source code in the same output and so
源代码在同一输出中，因此
coming back to item how did we solve it
回到项目我们如何解决它
this problem of supporting Java 9 with
支持Java 9的问题
altered version of item
项目的变更版本
since Java 9 in terms of byte codes
自Java 9以来的字节码
brings only model info which doesn't
仅带来没有的模型信息
contain any methods that we are
包含我们所使用的任何方法
interested in because it doesn't contain
感兴趣，因为它不包含
any methods we can pretend that each
我们可以假装的任何方法
time when we see Java 9 bytecode we
我们看到Java 9字节码的时间
actually see a Java 8 byte code so I
实际看到一个Java 8字节代码，所以我
assume we'll be able to read this
假设我们将能够阅读此
bytecode we will transform it as we want
字节码，我们将根据需要对其进行转换
and then in order to to hide this this
然后为了隐藏这个
little trick we will upgrade the class
小技巧，我们将升级课程
file version back so everybody outside
文件版本回来，所以外面的每个人
will see ok it was Java 9 it is giovanna
将会看到确定，它是Java 9，它是giovanna
but internally we we we're dealing with
但在内部，我们正在与之打交道
it as Java 8 that was the trick and at
就像Java 8一样
this moment of time please breathe a
这时候请呼吸
little bit this was just a little
一点点，这只是一点点
warm-up I hope now your brain is warm it
热身，我希望你的大脑现在温暖了
enough we have not that much time so we
足够，我们没有那么多时间，所以我们
will try to go even quicker and a little
会尝试更快一点
bit of hardcore stuff and please try to
一点硬核的东西，请尝试
follow me let's say I have such class
跟我说我有这样的课
this class have a static initializer
此类有一个静态初始值设定项
init in this static initializer we call
我们在这个静态初始化程序中初始化
construction of some other object of
其他一些对象的构造
some class and we call a method on it
一些类，我们在其上调用方法
some other class is actually a child of
其他班级实际上是
this base class and it has a method in
这个基类，它在
in this method we do an assertion is one
在这种方法中，我们做一个断言是
equal to 2 and and then we rerun all
等于2，然后我们重新运行所有
this so a question for you what is going
这对你来说是个问题
to happen if if I execute this and I say
如果我执行了这个然后我说
ok assertions a neighborhood
好的断言邻里
come on your brain should be warmed up
来吧，你的大脑应该热身
already assertions enabled we have an
已经启用断言，我们有一个
assertion one equal to two it's it's
断言一等于二是
obviously wrong they're going to be an
显然是错误的，他们将成为
exception it's easy
例外，这很容易
what about assertions disabled it will
那禁用断言呢
just run who thinks that it will just
刚跑的人以为会
run yeah it will just run but
是的，它将运行
unfortunately it will throw exception
不幸的是它将抛出异常
and the reason for this if we again
以及我们再次这样做的原因
recall how assertions enabled there is a
回想一下如何启用断言
static final field assertions disabled
静态最终字段断言已禁用
it is initialized in a static
它在静态中初始化
initializer and if you follow the
初始化程序，如果您遵循
sequence of of of execution what what is
执行顺序是什么
going to happen in order to insulite
为了发生insulite
child we need to first insulite base
孩子，我们需要第一个胰岛素基础
during consolidation of base we go to
在合并基础期间，我们去
child and cause a method so actually
孩子，实际上导致一种方法
this method is going to be called before
该方法将在之前被调用
the initialization of a child and
一个孩子的初始化和
science it's called before installation
安装前称为科学
of a child this field has a default
对于一个孩子，此字段具有默认值
value and the default value in java for
值和java中的默认值
boolean is false so assertion disabled
布尔值为假，因此禁用断言
but false is the state when this method
但此方法为假状态
will be called and you're gonna get
将被称为，你会得到
assertion here why this and such a
在这里断言为什么这样和这样的
situation we call it a bad cycle why
这种情况我们称其为不良循环
this is important because we base it our
这很重要，因为我们以此为基础
implementation on the same trick as a
实施与
surgeon's and so what happens with in
外科医生的，那么在发生什么
case of bad cycles for jacoco we are
jacoco的糟糕周期的情况下，我们
gonna get exactly the same problem our
会遇到完全相同的问题
field is going to have a default value
字段将具有默认值
default value for bullion arrays is now
金银阵列的默认值现在是
so we're going to get a null pointer
所以我们将得到一个空指针
exception how do we solve this okay we
例外，我们该如何解决呢？
solve this we introduce another
解决这个问题，我们介绍另一个
synthetic method which we call in its
合成方法，我们称之为
allies ation instead of accessing field
联盟而不是进入战场
directly we always go to this method
直接我们总是去这种方法
this method checks if there is some
此方法检查是否有一些
value then just returns this value if
值，然后返回该值
there is no such value that's in its
它没有这样的价值
allies and these
盟友和这些
Issus is a good order of initialization
Issus是初始化的好命令
oh yeah any problem with with this
哦，这个有什么问题吗
solution
解
anyone is it okay to do like this what
任何人都可以这样做
multi trading on the site of Jaco
Jaco网站上的多重交易
current I'm basically in this place
目前我基本上在这个地方
where we call in to jackar on time to
我们准时打电话到Jackar
get an array we have a synchronization
得到一个数组，我们有一个同步
so if - we'll try to install ice at the
因此，如果-我们将尝试在
same time it's going to be okay not
同时不会没事的
going to try them now okay in order to
现在要尝试他们，以便
go faster let me speed up the process if
走得更快，如果有的话，让我加快流程
you will go to Java Virtual Machine
您将转到Java虚拟机
specification into specification of put
规格转化为看跌规格
static we will find that you can call
静态的，我们会发现您可以致电
put static only feel if a field is final
仅在字段为final时才放静态
and you : it puts that exam this put
和你：这把考试
static instruction must occur in the so
静态指令必须出现在
called class initialization method
称为类初始化方法
otherwise an illegal access here is
否则这里是非法访问
strong and if we look back on our
坚强，如果我们回头看
example actually this is a final field
示例实际上这是一个最终字段
it is static so in order to in so as it
它是静态的，以便于如此
we call a put static and this has been
我们称看跌期权为静态，这是
working for for many years because
工作了很多年，因为
apparently it was never checked and it
显然它从未被检查过
started to be check out since gdk9 your
由于gdk9您开始检查
Lexus built for class files of Java 9
为Java 9的类文件构建的Lexus
version so yeah so we needed a proper
版本，是的，所以我们需要一个适当的
fix for this and after many many years
为此解决了很多年
we what we did we simply remove at the
我们所做的只是在
final now it works
现在终于可以了
what about interfaces one could say that
那接口呢？
there is no such problems for interfaces
接口没有这种问题
because everything is ok everything is
因为一切都很好
static final we can initialize fields in
静态最终，我们可以初始化字段
static initializer interfaces they don't
他们没有的静态初始化接口
have method so but cycles can't a curve
有方法，但循环不能弯曲
is interfaces but nope what about Java 8
是接口，但不，关于Java 8
in Java it you do have
在Java中，您确实拥有
methods in interfaces you have default
您具有默认接口的方法
methods and so probably the the bad
方法，所以可能是坏的
cycles can can occur with interfaces as
接口可能会发生循环
well in order to confirm this let's go
为了确认这一点，让我们开始吧
to the Java language specification
Java语言规范
let's read when insulation a course
让我们阅读隔热课程时
class or interface and Salas it
类或接口和萨拉斯
immediately before instance of the class
紧接该类实例之前
created or static method declared by the
创建或静态方法声明
classes invoked and when class in so why
类被调用以及何时在类中为什么
is it any super interfaces that declare
是否声明了任何超级接口
any default methods are also in so acid
任何默认方法也是如此
this is what Java language specification
这是Java语言规范
says let's try to write a bad cycle with
说让我们尝试用
interfaces so we will trigger
接口，所以我们将触发
initialization by creating an instance
通过创建实例进行初始化
similarly to example of classes we will
与类的示例类似，我们将
have some base interface in order to
有一些基本接口，以便
trigger its installation we will have
触发其安装，我们将拥有
default method in it in order to trigger
为了触发默认方法
a bad cycle we again will have a call
糟糕的周期，我们将再次致电
into the child into as a child method
入子成子方法
and we will have a child in a child we
我们将有一个孩子
will have some output on it static
会有一些静态输出
initialization and we will have this
初始化，我们将有这个
method and expected outcomes out of this
方法和预期结果
is either we will see exception and so
是要么我们会看到异常等等
the stack trace of from where this
从哪里的堆栈跟踪
method was called either we will see it
方法被调用或者我们将看到它
before the line static initialization
行静态初始化之前
happening or we will see it after if we
发生，否则我们会看到它
see it before them then this is
在他们面前看到它，然后这是
confirmations of bad cycle these
这些不良周期的确认
interfaces is possible if we see it
如果看到的话，接口是可能的
after then but cycleways interfaces is
之后，但cycleways接口是
not possible so what do you think is
不可能，所以你认为是什么
happening when we call such code is it
当我们调用这样的代码时发生的事情是
before or after who is for static
在谁为静态之前或之后
initialization happens before the call
初始化发生在调用之前
of the method ok who thinks after
谁想的方法好
who thinks that it will crash okay I
谁认为它会崩溃好吗
actually think it depends and that's why
其实认为这取决于，这就是为什么
I raised my hand three times it actually
我实际上举了三遍
depends if you take a GDK version before
取决于您之前是否使用了GDK版本
JDK 8 update 40 then you're gonna get
JDK 8更新40，那么您将得到
these seconds if you and you actually
这几秒钟，如果你和你实际上
going to get a crash because you're
会崩溃，因为你
trolling can exception so at the moment
拖钓可能会例外，因此目前
of throwing an exception you're going to
引发异常
get crushed interestingly if you
有趣的是，如果你被压碎
initialize through a call of a static
通过静态调用进行初始化
method you're gonna get another order so
方法您将要再下一个订单
it even was inconsistent if you do check
如果您检查的话甚至不一致
our Laxus built of GDK eight update then
我们的GDK内置的Laxus会更新为8
you're gonna see the correct order where
你会看到正确的顺序
it was fixed and this is how how easy to
它是固定的，这是多么容易
catch a back in GDK and this one was
赶回GDK，这是
catered by us and we reported it and
由我们提供，我们报告了
that's why it was fixed so for
这就是为什么要修复的原因
interfaces we still need to support this
接口我们仍然需要支持
case of that order so for interfaces
该顺序的情况如此，对于接口
there is a little bit more sophisticated
有一点更复杂
strategy we can't make this field non
策略，我们不能使该字段为非
final because everything can interface
最后，因为一切都可以接口
it should be final so we restore the
它应该是最终的，所以我们恢复
final but now we need to to prevent
最后，但现在我们需要防止
writing to this field and so we use
写这个领域，所以我们用
static initialization but before the
静态初始化，但在
static initialization happens we still
静态初始化发生，我们仍然
need to get the array so we have a slow
需要获取数组，所以我们的速度很慢
pass without assignment for for some GDK
通过一些GDK而未分配通过
versions we run out of time I'm sorry
版本用完我们很抱歉
for that we are going to quick quickly
为此，我们将很快
finish the last interesting question for
完成最后一个有趣的问题
how Java code coverage works is a
Java代码覆盖的工作原理是
runtime access in OSGi world you know
您知道的OSGi世界中的运行时访问
you have a class loaders discus loaders
你有一个类装载机铁饼装载机
they can restrict access to a certain
他们可以限制访问某些
classes and provides to only some such
类并仅提供一些此类
that you
那你
requested in particular let's say we
特别要求我们说我们
have implementation of such a
有这样的实现
restrictive class loader it gives you an
限制性的类加载器，它为您提供了
access obviously to to everything which
显然可以访问所有
is java.lang which is based Java and
是基于Java的java.lang和
also to some your application classes
也对您的某些应用程序类
lion concern package but it restricts
狮子关心包裹，但是限制
access to everything casts in particular
访问所有特别演员
it restricts access to to two jacoco
它限制了访问两个雅各布
package so how do we actually call our
包，所以我们实际上如何称呼我们的
runtime from the instrumented class
检测类的运行时
which was loaded by this class model
该类模型已加载
this is a problem what page the class
这是一个问题，什么课上
loader yes one way we can page the class
loader是一种我们可以上课的方式
loader it can be tricky and actually we
加载程序可能很棘手，实际上我们
have a way simpler solution as we have a
有一个更简单的解决方案，因为我们有一个
Java agent started before everything
Java代理先于一切
else we can actually page some class in
否则我们实际上可以在
in Java rank and all the class loaders
在Java排名和所有类加载器中
they do have access to Java rank as they
他们确实可以访问Java等级
do not restrict this so what we do we
不要限制这个，所以我们做什么
simply create a special field in one of
只需在其中一个创建一个特殊字段
Java classes and I never told you so
Java类，我从没告诉过你
there is actually no such field actually
实际上没有这样的领域
to be more precise this is we already
更确切地说，这是我们已经
change it a name of this class it's it's
更改它的名称，因为它是
no more this class I wouldn't tell you
我不会再告诉你这堂课
which one now it is and then so as we
现在是哪一个，然后像我们一样
can't access anything outside of Java we
无法访问Java以外的任何内容
also don't have an interface to call our
也没有界面可以调用我们的
runtime so we need to do this somehow
运行时，所以我们需要以某种方式执行此操作
differently and and so we speculate on
不同，所以我们推测
equals method this jacoco access is just
等于此jacoco访问权限的方法
an object this object has not that much
一个对象，这个对象没有那么多
methods it has only equals method so we
方法只有相等方法，所以我们
pass parameters through an array of
通过数组传递参数
objects and array is just an object so
对象和数组只是一个对象，所以
we can pass it a quick question how how
我们可以通过一个简单的问题
do we get a result back how do we get
我们会得到结果吗？
a prop array back equals method returns
一个prop数组返回equals方法返回
boolean we need an array yes thankfully
布尔值，我们需要一个数组，谢天谢地
in Java arrays immutable so we can we
在Java数组中是不可变的，所以我们可以
can we can simply speculate on the fact
我们可以简单地推测事实
that runtime will modify this array and
该运行时将修改此数组，并
this is how we do hopefully you had some
这就是我们的方式，希望您有一些
fun during this presentation don't
在这个演讲中的乐趣不要
hesitate to get involved don't hesitate
犹豫参与不要犹豫
to test early access builds of GDK and
测试GDK的早期访问版本，并
report bugs
报告错误
now that you know internals please help
现在您知道内部结构，请帮助
us answering some user questions where
我们在哪里回答一些用户问题
reflection doesn't work etc etc on Stack
反射不起作用等在堆栈上等
Overflow as well don't hesitate to join
溢出也不要犹豫
development of Eclipse echo Emma project
Eclipse echo Emma项目的开发
and jacoco projects and that's it thank
和jacoco项目，仅此而已
you for your attention
您的关注
and if you have any questions as we
如果您有任何疑问，我们
don't have time please catch me
没有时间请抓紧我
somewhere outside
外面的某个地方